builtbybuffalo.com 2010-01-11

# Buffalo - Brighton based interactive web design, development & e-commerce

### Privacy

Your use of this site implies your agreement and acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree please refrain from providing us with any personal information. 

####  Personal information

We may ask for personal information when you interact with the site. This information is held securely and can only be accessed by Buffalo.   
Despite these measures, please make sure you keep your information safe at all times as we are not responsible for the actions of third parties. 

####  Logs

We store information on site visitors only to provide usage statistics. None of the information is personal or could in anyway be linked to an individual or company. The information gathered will be used to improve the site and the user experience. 

####  Personal details

We do not sell, trade or transfer your personal information in any form to third parties unless ordered by a legal entity. We are the only people who have access to this data and we promise to keep it that way. 

####  Links

There are external links on our site and we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these websites. We cannot be liable for the contents and activities of these websites. 

####  Cookies

We do not currently use cookies on this site, however this may change in the future. Rest assured though, we will not use this data for anything other than monitoring our site. No personal details are recorded. 

####  Choices and opt-out

Should you no longer wish to hear from us (we will be sorry to see you go!) send us an email to [hello@builtbybuffalo.com](mailto:hello@builtbybuffalo.com "hello@builtbybuffalo.com") and we will remove you from our correspondence list. Likewise if you want to update your details - let us know and we will be happy to oblige. 

####  Future policy changes

This policy may evolve over time and we reserve the right to carry out any changes and request that you visit this page regularly, as these changes may affect you as a visitor to our site. 

####  Questions?

If you have questions about this privacy policy or the privacy aspects of our services please contact us by email at [hello@builtbybuffalo.com](mailto:hello@builtbybuffalo.com "hello@builtbybuffalo.com") or phone us on +44 (0)845 466 0030.

### Latest news

E-commerce

We often get asked about starting an e-commerce business - it can be confusing so hopefully this will help to make things a little clearer around the technical bits.

Less Copy Please!

Most people read differently when online, whereas reading a newspaper may be more of a cover to cover experience the web needs to have concise content that allows skim reading. 

More on our blog

### Twitter Feed

Merry Christmas from all at Buffalo...enjoy!  
Posted 25th December, 2009
